Hello.
How are you?
All good?
Congratulations to all the winners.
Super, super proud.
I'm nobody to tell this.
But thank you so much for all your hard work.
And I'm so glad to be here.
Thank you so much for all of you inviting
me.
Thank you, means a lot.
So I had one speech prepared for the gathering,
but I don't know if somewhere someone had
told me you have to tell your, you know, life
story.
Anyway.
So I don't think my life story is good enough
for this gathering.
So what I'm going to do is it's called SHE
Empowerment.
Where do I start?
Okay.
So, generally, I've been called, you know,
"the smiling Queen," or something they say
out there, but is it too loud? should I?
Is it fine?
Okay.
So yeah, like I was saying, I always been
called "the smiling Queen."
And I, yes, of course, I always, always keep
smiling.
For all the love I get for all the appreciation
I get from all of you who watch my films.
But you know, one of the other reasons why
I smile?
All of us, I'm pretty sure that all the girls
here, smile through the sadness, through the
loneliness, through the anger, through the
frustration, smile is a superpower, you know.
Yeah, same thing with me.
I keep doing it, and one day, I keep thinking,
I'll keep smiling till that day where my smile
turns into a real one from the heart.
But yes, this is a superpower.
And that's why women are, I think, the most
pure.
I don't know, I don't know how to say the
mother is a purest being in the whole world
is what they say, right?
Yeah.
I'm so glad to be born a girl.
I'm so glad to be born a girl in this generation.
Having such people protect us with all that
they've got.
I don't know.
I'm just super glad, super proud, and yeah,
well.
So let me just start introducing myself.
I'm Rashmika.
For all those who know me a big, big Hi!
And for all those who don't well, I'm an actor
in the southern industry, and I hope soon
you all get to know me as well.
That's for my introduction.
I don't think I should go on more on that.
Well, since I was a really small girl, I still
remember all that my mother said was you should
never let someone else see you angry, see
you cry, see you feel any of the negative
emotions because apparently, that's, that's
showing your weakness, right?
That's what my mom has always told me.
And I think that's one of the reasons why
I just don't know what else to do now.
I actually genuinely do not know how to cry.
Do you know that?
Like, I have to work so hard to actually cry
on screen, I cannot do it.
And I look like an idiot when I cry on stage.
I mean cry on screen, I'm sorry.
So yeah, I think that is the one thing I can't
do.
But I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
what to say nowadays I see women doing so
many things.
Women accomplishing so many things in different
fields.
And I feel too little.
I feel like, what am I doing?
I don't know.
Is it good enough?
Is it enough for me to get all of this love
and appreciation for something so small that
I'm doing?
I don't know.
I don't.
I still feel like this is not enough, and
I want to do a lot more.
And well, I'm just a girl from a small town
in Karnataka called Virajpet in Kodagu district.
I don't know if you guys are aware of it.
From there I don't know how my life has happened.
I don't know at the age of 23; I'm here talking
to such a gathering.
But I'm, I'm glad that I am, and I don't know
if I want to say that I'm proud of myself
yet because I don't think I'm done yet.
I've just started, and I feel like I'm in
the process of getting myself a huge, big
loving kingdom that I'm going to create for
myself.
And why I started saying this is if I, a girl
from Kodagu, can do this then imagine you
guys from Hyderabad what you're capable of.
I think women are capable of doing anything
they want in this world.
And I hope one day all of you make your dreams
come true.
Please dream big.
I'm sorry if the speech is too boring.
But I just want to say, dream big, do not
give a break, keep working hard, keep working
hard.
It's okay if someone is laughing at you.
It's okay if someone is pulling your leg,
pulling you back down, it's okay.
You just keep working hard.
You just keep looking up at the sky and reach
your goals no matter what anyone else says.
Because if you cannot protect yourself and
dream for yourself, nobody else can.
Truly, trust me.
I've been there.
I've done that, and now I'm in the process
of getting there, and I think I will get there
pretty soon.
I hope all of you join me and thank you so
much for doing such a wonderful program like
this and having me as a part of it.
Means a lot, feel really, I'm truly grateful
honestly.
Thank you so much, and sorry if I have bored
you.
But I just wanted to say we are here to protect
you, and I hope you reach your dreams you
make your dreams come true.
Thank you.